To be continued
It's for the gold of the market.
It's a small matter.
If he calls me again,
let him tell me where he is.
I will call him myself.
Let him tell the truth.
Sir, Sir Kajorn is here.
Hey, it's not Sir Kajorn.
It's his gun.
Sir Kajorn isn't here.
That's right.
Sir Kajorn.
Hello.
Please have a seat.
What do you have for me
Here.
This is the real gold from Russia.
It's from us.
It's really beautiful, my dear friend.
Actually,
I have to give you one.
Because China has a lot of gold.
It's a lot.
China has a lot of gold.
What about the rest of the money?
That's all.
Let's go.
It's really beautiful.
I want to give it to you.
Sir.
Please give me the money.
Thank you so much.
How much do you want?
Take this money and give it to Tin.
You said you were going to bet with Samart.
Who is more important?
Again?
You are talking about this again.
How do you know?
I won't change my mind from Samart.
Even if they win the game,
they will be champions all the time.
There is no way to replace Samart.
They will win.
Samart is the best.
Samart won't die.
He will die.
This is mine.
This is yours.
I have another friend.
When I was in the army,
I was in a new position.
I have a gun in my hand.
If I don't have a gun, I will shoot.
Wherever I am,
I have to be next to him.
If I kill someone,
I will be dead.
You must be crazy.
You are a police officer.
Three years ago,
you must have heard a lot of news
and caught a lot of criminals.
Chaya, the gunman,
his name is Ja Thanong.
If you want to know who these two are,
let them shoot together.
I also want to know
who the gunman is.
What do you think?
It's not a bad idea.
But in recent years,
there may be a new gunman
in the army.
If you want to know the truth,
send a letter
to the head of the army
so we can know who is better.
Okay.
I am confident.
They must be one.
They must be together
for the rest of their lives.
They must be worth
what they deserve.
One more thing.
They will come here
Here, 10 million baht
for the winner.
You and I will get half of it.
And for the two of us,
we should get the same amount.
That's good, my friend.
Sometimes,
when the sky is open,
there is a prize in a pickup truck.
But most of the time,
the prize is only
the word of fortune.
I want you to send
a letter to the gunman
so we can know
who is better than the gunman.
That's good.
Call him.
The prize is 50,000 baht
for this letter.
The date,
the time,
the details
are all in this envelope.
I want 80,000 baht.
Tell him
that if he doesn't get it,
he should hire someone else.
It's too expensive.
80,000 baht.
Give it back to me.
Okay.
And find someone else.
I'll talk to him.
I'll give it to you.
Here, 30,000 baht.
What about the price?
How much do you want?
You already got 20,000 baht.
What 20,000 baht?
When did you give it to me?
Don't lie to me.
This job
is worth 100,000 baht.
You gave me 50,000 baht.
I gave you 80,000 baht.
You still have 20,000 baht left.
Don't do this to me.
You can't do this to me.
After next week,
I'll send a letter
to the gunman.
Otherwise, I'll be in trouble.
Let's get out of here.
What are you doing?
Please leave.
What do you want?
Do you hear me?
Please leave.
What do you want?
I don't want to leave.
Don't you know what you're saying?
Get out
or I'll throw you out.
What did you say?
You want to fight me?
I accept the challenge.
Let's play a game.
Arachun,
there's still a game left.
How about 200,000 baht?
Fine.
You're really bad.
It's not that hard.
But you have to pay a little.
How about 500,000 baht?
No problem.
This time,
you're really bad.
It's okay.
Let him drink.
Then he'll get drunk
and you'll be in trouble.
Let's go.
Wait for me over there.
I'm coming.
He's starting to get drunk.
It's not easy.
Of course.
I'm sorry.
It's too hard.
I'm going to puke.
We've spent more than 10,000 baht.
Don't go to hell.
Don't get drunk.
He's going to get drunk.
He's not drunk.
He's going to puke.
Look at him.
I'm going to drink.
He's done.
He's drunk.
He's going to puke.
Don't cry.
Is he lying to me?
He's drunk.
How can he be lying to you?
I want to know too.
He's so drunk.
Do you still remember him?
You have to be careful.
I'm not afraid of anything.
You'll see.
Why are you crying?
I told you I'm not afraid of anything.
Come on.
What are you doing?
I told you I'm not afraid of anything.
Let's go.
We've run out of money.
The money is with us.
Let's go.
Stop.
He's going to lie to me.
You're going to lie to me.
You're still weak.
Let's go.
Take this money and send it to my mother and wife.
Here's your money.
Keep it.
What about you?
Don't worry.
I'm going to be drunk one day.
I can find a new one tomorrow.
Where are you going?
I have a big job.
If I succeed,
I won't be completely drunk.
Don't worry.
Let's go home.
This is the last one.
This is the last coin.
Don't worry.
It's all gone.
This is nothing.
It's so good.
Let's go to the city and buy more.
It's so cute.
I'll buy it for you.
Let's go.
I'm going to sell it all.
It's got a lot of money.
It's got both the car and the money.
Be careful.
It's got a lot of money.
I'm selling good stuff today.
I can't sell my stuff.
Can you help me buy it?
Can you help me buy this toy?
It's not expensive.
1,000 baht is enough.
I have one.
But I can't sell it.
No one will buy it.
I'm not sure if I can sell it today.
Here it is.
This is the real stuff.
Take it.
You might like it.
Where are you?
Take all the money you can sell.
Send it to me.
Or you'll die.
Oh, brother.
The gun is not loaded yet.
You!
My turn.
Can you walk?
You look so weak.
You have to continue.
Why did I do that?
You have a bad smell.
Don't touch it.
My nails are so sharp.
Your nails are sharp.
That's why I changed it for you.
Don't you like it?
I don't like it.
Your nails are long.
It's too long.
You guys are not brave enough.
Get out of here.
Don't let me get used to you.
I told you to get out of here.
Can't you hear me?
Get out of here.
My son.
I'm running out of money.
I told you I don't have money.
Can't you hear me?
You guys fight.
Don't cry, Tangkwa.
Tangkwa.
Don't cry.
My son is rich.
I don't have money to take him to the doctor.
I told you I don't have money to take him to the doctor.
I don't know what to do.
Tangkwa, my son.
It's so hot.
I have to go now.
Take my son to the doctor.
Thank you very much.
Remember, my son.
Sometimes we have to help the one who suffers the most.
Do you understand, my son?
If I defeat you,
what will I get in return from you, Han?
My life is easy.
My life is the same as before.
And your name, Thana-ling,
will be forgotten.
You can defeat me.
It's too little.
I want something that's more than that.
Okay.
Then who will you offer the money to?
I don't want you to die, my son.
I just want to teach you.
I just want the gun you use.
Okay.
You will get everything you want.
Is everyone ready?
Yes.
Han, let's get started.
Let's get started.
Do you think you're the owner of this gun?
No.
I don't want to die.
Sir.
Doctor needs to see Han.
This time,
gunmen all over Thailand
will come together.
It won't be difficult to find,
and you will know
that I am the only one.
I heard the news that Sir Kajorn has been sent out to look for Khan again.
That's for sure. Sir Kajorn is afraid that I will die.
He kills Khan and I kill Thanoong.
These two have similar skills.
But the fate of Khan and Kajorn is still with me.
I'm sure that Thanoong will win.
What if Thanoong is looking for someone?
No, he has to come. Otherwise, he will be killed.
Have you sent a letter to Thanoong yet?
I went to his house. The man there said that Thanoong had been gone for a long time.
I think I will leave the police.
You are going to die.
No, Thanoong, you have to find Thanoong.
I have to be the winner.
That red bottle must belong to you.
Do you understand?
Yes, Sir.
Please help my son.
Drop your gun. It will kill my son.
Please help my son. Drop your gun.
Don't shoot.
Drop your gun.
Please help my son.
Did you have a nightmare again?
You have been like this for three years.
When will you be able to do something?
I don't understand.
Why do I have to be in your memory all the time?
If you are like this all the time,
I feel uncomfortable.
I understand.
I am afraid that my son will be affected by the poison.
I will try.
Sometimes I can make my son better.
Please eat.
Thanoong,
I believe in you.
I am sure that you will win.
Don't say that.
I can't go.
I have to leave this world.
You should think about it.
You have 10 million baht.
You can go to any country.
I have told you.
I have left him.
I will never go back to him.
It's okay.
You can think about it.
If you change your mind,
on the 17th,
we will meet at the temple.
I will wait for you there.
I told you to contact the gunmen.
I sent the letter by myself.
They all want the prize money.
But there is still a problem.
What is the problem?
The man you told me to follow.
He can't come.
Why can't he come?
According to the man,
he said that Thanoong
shot a man to death.
He was very sad.
So he left the police.
He ran away from the police.
He ran away from his wife.
No!
Thanoong must be shot.
Otherwise, I will lose my face.
Thanoong,
no matter what you do,
whether you are dead or alive,
you must shoot Thanoong.
Yes, sir.
I will follow him.
Thanoong,
there is no way that you can eat that.
Eat, eat, eat.
Don't eat too much.
Our child will be strong.
Don't worry.
He will be as stubborn as his father.
Try to guess.
Our child will be a woman.
Of course.
He must be a man.
Last night,
I talked to him.
Are you crazy?
I think it's a woman.
The child is in my belly.
If the child is a woman,
when he grows up,
I will let him be a nurse.
When we get old,
he will take care of us.
If he is a man,
what do you want him to be?
A man?
Tell me.
Anything is fine.
Just one thing.
Don't let him be like you.
How are you, my son?
Yes, brother.
My son has a high fever.
I will take him to the city.
I'm afraid he won't be able to go.
Please leave it to me.
My son,
go to the city.
I will take care of him.
Thank you, my son.
Brother,
please take care of my son.
Don't worry.
You're sick, my son.
Here.
I can't see you.
Drink it.
You can't drink it.
You have to drink it.
Are you done?
Grandpa.
Wait.
Take my money.
Where can I get it?
Wait here.
I'll get it in the village.
No.
Wait here.
I'll be right back.
Don't cry.
Be patient.
It's just a little fever.
Don't cry.
Is it a prank?
It's so hot.
Why is it so hot?
You've lived with me for many years.
You're very familiar with me.
But this time,
I need you.
My son's life is very important to me.
I'll come back
and take you back.
My son.
Wait.
Your son
is very sick.
I'm afraid he's going to die.
So I took him
to the village.
Thank you
for saving my son's life.
No problem.
What's wrong?
Before I bought you
I didn't have money
to buy you the medicine.
Let's go.
Two bottles of wine.
Yes.
Drink it.
Take the medicine.
Be careful.
Drink slowly.
Don't cry.
It's not water.
You don't have to worry.
You can drink as much as you want.
I'll take you home.
Look.
There are many
who want to
shoot me.
Let me warn you.
Don't go there.
Go back and die.
Not just me.
I killed hundreds of people.
You won't get there.
Go back.
Ten million is mine.
You have no right.
If you want,
you can shoot me here.
What did I say?
Who taught you that?
Who shot me here?
If you dare,
shoot me here.
If you're scared, die.
Who shot you?
It's him.
Can't you see?
The smoke coming out of his shirt.
It's him.
The real one.
He shot so fast
that people couldn't see.
I called everyone
to come here today.
I have an offer
for you to consider.
I believe
that all of you here
know each other well.
Han and Ja Thanong.
They have
a lot of gun skills.
In the era of gunmen,
everyone knows each other well.
What does it have to do with us?
Let's say that
one of you
faces someone.
Do you think
you can fight them?
I'm not sure.
It's true that Han and Ja Thanong
have skills.
But if we're scared,
we won't come here.
You're right.
No one is scared of anyone.
But everyone will accept the truth
that the chance to win
is small.
Why?
Are you afraid?
Or do you want us
to give up?
No, no, no.
I don't mean that.
I want you to think
that if you're in the battlefield,
you have more power
than the opposition.
But not just one person.
I believe that
more power
can be used.
You want us to
give up?
That's right.
What about 10 million?
You have only 6 people.
You can share 10 million.
You'll get it.
Don't worry.
Think about it.
Don't lose your life.
You'll get another million.
Everyone,
I want you
to do me a favor.
What is it?
Tanong won't
be shot.
I need him.
I think you can help me.
Your husband
is stubborn.
I'll use you
as a tool.
Don't worry.
I won't hurt you.
Tanong will be shot.
You'll be free.
He'll get 10 million.
Think about it.
I'm good.
Tanong is a good man.
Why do you have to force him?
It's not a big deal.
It's just a game.
The winner
will be the winner.
The loser will be the loser.
It's not a big deal.
Tanong,
go to the camp
and prepare the food.
I'll give you food.
On the 17th,
the gunfire will be broken.
I'm surprised
that I'm still alive.
You're strong.
That's why
I called you here.
I know everything.
This is
my greatest hope.
It's not just the food.
You'll get 10 million
from the winner.
I'll give you
5 million
if you can
kill one person
with your own hands.
Who?
This person is your important partner.
Tanong,
this person
is your important partner.
I believe in you.
5 million
for Tanong.
Don't worry.
Even if it's not worth anything,
I have to do it.
It's my life.
It's my soul.
It's everything to me.
I have to do it.
We haven't seen each other
for 3 years.
It's normal.
We have to improve.
Where have you been?
I've been abroad.
What do you want?
Are you going back to the police?
No.
I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
I'll tell you later.
==
What happened?
Didn't you see that
there was a shot from the air?
Damn.
I was waiting to see who would go to hell.
You scared me.
Teacher Tanong
wants to see you.
Tanong?
You should sit down.
Did you hear that, Lin?
I'm not here to argue with you.
I want to know where my wife is.
And what do you want from me?
I'm sorry.
We used to work together.
I wouldn't dare to have anything to do with you.
About your wife,
I didn't arrest her.
I didn't lock her up.
I brought her here.
Let's be honest.
It's nothing.
I just want you to use your power
to defeat all the gunmen.
It's not difficult at all.
If I don't do it,
what will happen?
Oh, you don't have to ask me.
You already know.
You have to force me
to arrest her one more time.
This is because I'm stupid.
You think too much.
Do it.
Think of it as a job.
You'll get both money and victory.
And you'll get your wife back.
Think about it.
In the end,
we did it.
We shot all the gunmen.
Let's celebrate
to get rid of all the gunmen.
Listen,
the gunmen are all over the place.
It's so exciting.
I'm telling you,
money doesn't stop.
It's ten million.
It's the same as us.
Don't even think about it.
Just one bullet will kill this house.
The gunmen I contacted
are here to protect you.
Come on.
Where's the gunmen?
Oh, my.
Hello, young man.
Do you see the gunmen?
Hey, young man.
Shoot them.
How can we trust them?
You can trust them.
The first one is from Srisaket.
He's a drug addict.
Oh, my.
You know how to shoot, don't you?
I'll show you.
Hold on.
Catch him.
Oh, Kimo.
You're in trouble.
I'll show you
I'm Inter.
Don't be shy.
Who are you talking to?
This is definitely the one.
I contacted him myself.
He looks scary. He looks very fierce.
I don't know anything about him.
Don't do it. Your hand will get hurt.
Ouch!
Don't use your hand.
Use that hand.
Ouch!
Don't use that hand.
What a sweet boy.
Ouch!
What's wrong?
He's a snake.
He's so cute.
Great!
Brother,
I didn't think I'd see you here again.
I didn't know
that you were here.
It's not good
to see you here.
I'm not feeling well.
I'm not feeling well at all.
Brother, you saved my son's life.
I...
Don't talk about him again.
Whatever happens,
it has to happen.
What everyone does
is their duty.
It's the duty
of everyone
who is a gunman.
But
you still have me
and my son's life
just like my life.
Enough.
I understand.
How about this?
If you want to
repay me,
can you do me a favor?
Anything you want.
Sit down and drink.
Be my friend.
I've never drunk
but for my brother.
What's going on?
Are you sleepy?
Tell them
that I'll call you again.
I'm at your house.
That's all.
Sir, I've called a hundred people.
Are you done?
I'll know
who's more certain
Han and Thanong.
Give this letter to Lieutenant Phan.
Tell him that Thanong gave it to you.
Dear, while my friend is reading this letter,
there was a shooting at Thamma Khang
near the train station.
I'm sorry that I didn't tell you
from the beginning.
The police will kill my wife.
But now,
I need your help.
I'll take you there in two hours.
Thanong.
Wait.
Take this letter
and open it in two hours.
Then follow me to the address.
Where is it?
I'm confused.
Don't wait too long.
Then we'll know
who's the gunman
and who's
the owner of this bottle.
I'm so happy.
Han must be the owner.
Thanong must win.
Han Tho Nung.
Han Tho Nung
Han Thon сами.
Han Tho Nung.
I bring you a note.
He's too young
to look like a child.
Stop drinking and come back
to get drunk.
Miss Vanine,
you better not
take anything here.
I'll eat the chicken as a child.
I'll eat you as a child.
Really?
Han! Han! Han!
Nung! Nung!
What are you talking about?
That's right.
Han!
There are four of us.
Nung, Han, Nung, and Nung.
These four are very dangerous.
If we join together, we can defeat them.
Remember, don't break the group.
Let's go.
Hey, you!
Drink. Drink.
Really?
You're so sexy.
Let's go.
I'll drink with you.
No, Han.
You're not important.
When we have fun with this game,
we just have fun.
That's all.
Yes, we're rich.
We have money.
We can do whatever we want.
You two go first.
No one can stop us.
I'm going to hit you.
Come on.
We're not dead yet.
We have rewards.
Do you think we're dogs or pigs?
You think we're toys?
You're as good as us.
Let's play together.
Don't, Han.
Don't kill me.
I'll give you more money than you can give me.
You know how much I have.
Tell me how much you want.
Tell me.
I'll give you the money.
Why?
I'll give it to you.
I found it.
Take this bag.
Here you go.
I'll give you 500.
Let's go.
No, 10 million.
Good luck.
We were born
with only one life.
But we have
two lives.
Because of him,
he saved my son's life.
I'll repay him.
From now on,
you have to take care of yourself.
Hanung.
This brother of yours helped me.
Thank you
for saving my life.
Brother, I don't want to
be shot
for 10 million.
I only want my wife back.
So,
this money
is yours.
Thank you again.
Next time, we'll meet again.
Let's go.
What is it, brother?
Tell me.
I came here
to get 10 million.
What I want
is a gun.
I have to defeat everyone.
I have to defeat
one person.
Brother,
you have won.
I'm not afraid.
I only want my wife back.
I don't want to be shot.
They say
that
whoever gets shot
will be killed.
It's useless.
Hanung has been dead
for many years.
I'm Hanung,
the only one.
If you don't stop,
you'll regret it.
Pond.
Pond!
Did you get shot by my gun?
What are you doing here at night?
This is illegal!
Drop the gun.
Don't shoot only
to stop it from这样.
Don't shoot.
Drop the gun!
If you want to be a gunman,
then 99.99%
with the support of
Petchpanna Production.